Finding aid for the James Coover papers Mus. Arc. 88
Coover (James) papers
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
James Burrell Coover papers
1943 2004
circa 1948-2004
Mus. Arc. 88
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
16 Linear Feet
(26 boxes)
Contains the personal papers of music librarian James Burrell Coover, including various materials related to his educational and employment history; his consultant work; personal and business-related correspondence; awards, grants and fellowships; his involvement in professional organizations such as International Association of Music Libraries and the Music Library Association; his associations with Vassar College and University at Buffalo (SUNY), both as music library director and professor of music; collected publications and research materials; and his published and unpublished materials.
Coover, James B. (James Burrell), 1925-2004
Box 1
Box 2
Box 3
Box 4
Box 5
Box 6
Box 7
Box 8
Box 9
Box 10
Box 11
Box 12
Box 13
Box 14
Box 15
Box 16
Box 17
Box 18
Box 19
Box 20
Box 21
Box 22
Box 23
Box 24
Box 25
Box 26
Accruals and Editions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in thirteen series: I. Personal Documents, 1950-2004; II. Consultancies, 1957-1986; III. Correspondence, 1948-2000; IV. Gifts, 1957-2001; V. Grants and Fellowships, 1979-1997; VI. Professional Organizations, 1955-1980; VII. University at Buffalo, 1967-2000; VIII. Vassar College, 1953-1967; IX. Collected Publications and Research Materials; X. Publications, 1951-2001; XI. Unpublished Materials, 1953-1994; XII. Manuscripts; XIII. Other related material.
Biographical Note
James Burrell Coover (born June 3, 1925 in Jacksonville, IL; died May 28, 2004 in Williamsville, NY) earned his B.A. and M.A. in music theory at the University of North Colorado and an M.A. in library science from the University of Denver. Over the course of his library science degree, he also served as the Assistant Director of the Biographical Center for Research, Rocky Mountain Region in Denver.
After completing the library science degree in 1953, Coover became Director of the George Sherman Dickinson Music Library at Vassar College and taught courses in the music department, including music bibliography and jazz history. His strong interest in contemporary music led him to found Vassar's Faculty Study Group on Avant-Garde music in 1965. While at Vassar, he also became involved with the Hudson Valley Philharmonic as a performing percussionist from 1959 to 1967 and served as the personnel and special concerts manager of the organization.
He first became associated with the State University at Buffalo (SUNY) in 1967, where he served as a professor of music and the director of the Music Library until his retirement in 1999. While at Buffalo, he established a dual master's degree program in music librarianship with associate music librarian Carol June Bradley, taught the department's course in music bibliography, and developed an extensive research collection. He chaired the music department from the years 1974-1976 and 1978-1981; was named the Birge-Carey Professor from 1974-1976 and 1978-1981; held the Ziegele professorship from 1981-1999; was an adjunct professor in the School of Information and Library Science from 1980-1999; and was named a SUNY Distinguished Service Professor in 1992. Outside of UB, Coover was a consultant at several private and middle states institutions from 1957 to 1992. He was also actively involved in the Music Library Association, serving as President (1959-1960) and on the Board of Directors (1987-1990), the Publications Committee (1956-1958, 1966-1969, 1975-1978), and the Finance Committee (1967-1969, 1976-1980).
Coover is the author and editor of numerous writings, spanning over thirty published articles; various book and record reviews, essays, and pamphlets; and ten books. These cover topics related to music lexicography, music bibliography, music publishing and printing, antiquarian catalogues, discographies of jazz and medieval music, musical instrument collections, music theory, and collection development. These include Music Lexicography; Including a Study of Lacunae in Music Lexicography and a Bibliography of Music Dictionaries (1958); Music Instrument Collections (1981); Music Publishing, Copyright, and Piracy in Victorian England: A Twenty-Five Year Chronicle, 1881-1906 (1985); Antiquarian Catalogs of Musical Interest (1988); Music at Auction: Puttick and Simpson (1988); and Private Music Collections: Catalogs and Cognate Literature (2001).
Terms of Access and Use
The James Burrell Coover papers are open to researchers.
Restrictions
Some items in the Manuscripts Bound Materials sub-series are restricted. Contact the Music Library archives for more information.
Acquisition Information
The collection was gifted to the Music Library by James Coover prior to his retirement in 1999.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of the personal papers of music librarian James Burrell Coover, including various materials related to his educational and employment history; his consultant work; personal and business-related correspondence; awards, grants and fellowships; his involvement in professional organizations such as International Association of Music Libraries and the Music Library Association; his associations with Vassar College and University at Buffalo (SUNY), both as music library director and professor of music; collected publications and research materials; and his published and unpublished materials. The collection includes text, manuscripts, photographs, photocopies, and book bound materials.
Academic librarians -- New York (State); Academic librarians -- New York (State) -- Faculty status; Correspondence; faculty papers; Library administration; Library science teachers -- Buffalo (N.Y.); Library science teachers -- United States; Music--Manuscripts; Scholarly publishing -- United States
- Personal documents, 1950 2004; 1950-2004; I (Box 1)
  - Appointment as Clerical Assistant III - Denver Public Library
  - Awards
  - Clippings
  - Curriculum Vitae
  - Employment documents, 1967 -
  - Funeral Program
  - New Grove Questionnaire for Musicologists
  - Photos
- Consultancies, 1957 1986; 1957-1986; II (Box 1, Box 2)
  - Consultancies
  - Consultancies - Bowker
  - Private
    - Union Theological Seminary Survey, 1959
    - Oberlin, 1957
    - Swarthmore, 1963
    - University of Louisville, 1968
    - USC, 1981
    - Notre Dame, 1986
    - New York City School of Visual Arts, 1978
    - Puerto Rico Consultancy, 1979
    - Westminster Choir College, 1965
  - Middle States
    - Philadelphia Musical Academy, 1961
    - Philadelphia Academy of Music, 1969
    - Philadelphia College of Art, 1969
    - Puerto Rico Conservancy of Music, Preliminary Survey, 1974
    - The New School of Music, 1975
    - Puerto Rico Conservancy of Music, 1975
    - Combs College of Music, 1981
- Correspondence, 1948 2000; 1948-2000; III (Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6)
  - A
  - ACMI Correspondence
  - Arneson, Arne
  - Articles and Letters
  - B
  - Baron
  - Bechwith, Bob
  - Bowles, Garrett
  - C
  - Campbell, Frank
  - Chase, Gilbert
  - Chronicle - Correspondence
  - Churgin, Betty
  - Cobbe, Hugh
  - Codere, Helene
  - Colby, Edward
  - Colvig, Richard
  - Coover, Chris
  - Coover, JB, Memos to
  - Coover, JB, Memos to/from Executive Committee, LAC, and others
  - Coral, Leonore
  - Cox, Lisa (Antiquarian Music, Books, etc.)
  - Crawford, David
  - Center for Research Libraries (CRL)
  - DaLuiso, Florence
  - Dictionary Society of North America
  - Distinguished Librarian (nomination of Carol June Bradley) - Correspondence
  - E
  - Erwin, Charlotte
  - Fine, Vivian
  - Fontes Artis Musicae
  - Fuld, James
  - G
  - Galloway, Kenneth
  - Garland Publishing, Inc.
  - Gauntlett Catalogues
  - Gould, M.
  - H
  - Hall, George
  - Hassen Letters
  - Headrick re: Salaries '98
  - Helm, Everett
  - Hill, George
  - Hill, Richard (3)
  - Hillschrift
  - Hixon-Hennessee
  - Holiday Greetings - Correspondence
  - Holst, Imogen, 1907-1984
  - Jackson, Bruce
  - Job Offers/Notices - Correspondence
  - K
  - Kaufman, Judy
  - King, Alec d. 3-10-95
  - Kotonski, Wlodzimierz
  - Krummel, Don
  - L
  - Leinbach, Philip
  - Lenneberg, Hans
  - Levy, Ralph
  - Library Administrative Council - Correspondence
  - Lindahl
  - MAC - Mansell
  - Maguire, Janet
  - Manuscript - Part Book Leaves (Spencer, Robert)
  - Marco
  - McIntire, Dennis
  - McKinnon
  - Middle States at UB, 1980
  - Miller, Philip
  - Millers and New York Public Library
  - Mols, Robert
  - Montagu, Jeremy
  - Moretto, Kathleen
  - Music Library Archive
  - Naylor, John
  - NASM - Correspondence
  - Nomination of Jan Williams1983
  - Ochs, Michael
  - Ochs, m. - Antiq. Catalogues, 1988
  - Ossenkop, David
  - Parry, Charles
  - Pizer, Irwin
  - Plain Talk
  - Pruett
  - R
  - Rainbeau Catalog - Correspondence, Orders, Thanks
  - Recommendation, Selected, 1968-
  - Removal of Saktidas Roy 1984
  - Resource Support from the Music Department (UB) - Correspondence
  - Roberts, Don
  - Rorem, Ned
  - Rose, Gloria
  - Rosenthal
  - Rudhyar, Dane
  - S
  - Samuel, Harold E.
  - Sapp, Allen
  - Sartori, Claudio
  - Schneider, Mischa
  - Selden, Bernice
  - Smith, Carleton Sprague
  - Solow, Linda
  - Strahle, Graham
  - SUNY Union List - Correspondence with Saktidas Roy
  - Temporary Services Budget (UB) - Correspondence
  - Thomas, John
  - Thornton, Eileen
  - Taxonomy - Copies & Correspondence
  - Tinctoris - Correspondence, Study, etc.
  - Treasures of the Music Library - Correspondence with William Greiner
  - UB Foundation - Correspondence with Gail Paxson Mates
  - Wolff, Christoph
- Gifts, 1957 2001; 1957-2001; IV (Box 6)
  - Composers - ALS to JBC
  - Catalogue Collection, 1987
  - Gifts, 1980s
  - Gifts, 1990s
  - Gifts, 1991
  - Jazz (JC)
  - President's Associates
  - Pueblo County Historical Society
- Grants and fellowships, 1979 1997; 1979-1997; V (Box 7)
  - Awards
    - American Council of Learned Societies - 1982
    - Grants - SUNY, 1981, 1982
    - UB - Feasibility Study
    - Grant Stuff 1979
    - Grants JBC
    - National Endowment for the Humanities Grant Application 1988
    - National Endowment for the Humanities
  - Not Awarded
    - ACLS, 1982
    - ACLS, 1984/1985
    - ACLS, 1988
    - Bibliographical Society of America '88
    - Guggenheim, 1981
  - Grant Reviewer: Australian Research Council, 1997
  - Grants
  - Grants - JBC
- Professional organizations, 1955 1980; 1955-1980; VI (Box 8, Box 9)
  - International Association of Music Libraries (IAML)
  - Music Library Association
    - Annual Meeting: Buffalo, 1955
    - Annual Meeting: Ann Arbor (Midwinter), 1961
    - Annual Meeting: Washington, 1970
    - Annual Meeting: Washington, 1971
    - Annual Meeting: Washington, April 1971
    - Annual Meeting: Washington, February 1974
    - Annual Meeting: Toronto, February 1970
    - Annual Meeting: Seattle (Midwinter) 1976
    - Finance Committee, undated
    - Finance Committee, October 1977
    - Finance Committee Meeting (Philadelphia), 1980-09-18 1980-09-19; September 18-19, 1980
    - Committee on Standards, 1967
    - Meeting Stuff, Committee Reports
    - Publications Committee
    - Publications Committee, 1976
    - Publications Committee, September 1978
    - Standards Committee
    - Standards, Training
    - "Those Guys" Committee
    - Automation Committee - 1973
    - Program Committee
    - Correspondence: Bibliography Stuff - Krummel, Hill, et. al
    - Correspondence: Periodical Indexing 1
    - Correspondence: Periodical Indexing 2
    - Correspondence: Periodical Indexing - F. Kretzschmar
    - Correspondence: Periodical Indexing - Brooks Shepard
    - Correspondence: Periodical Indexing - Surveys and Studies
    - Correspondence: President's Term of Office
    - Correspondence: Research Libraries Group Program Committe
    - Presidency
  - National Association of Schools of Music Meeting, 1976
- University at Buffalo, 1967 2000; 1967-2000; VII (Box 9, Box 10, Box 11)
  - Committees
    - Arts & Letters Library Committee, 1987 1988; 1987-1988
    - Arts Management
    - Chancellor's Advisory Committee
    - Chancellor's Advisory Committee, 1976-77
    - Chancellor's Awards, 1978
    - Committees
    - Conferences in the Disciplines, 1994-95
    - Dean's Advisory Committee, 1994
    - Distinguished Service Professor Committee, 1996
    - Executive Committee - General
    - President's Review Board
    - President's Research Advisory Council, 1983
  - Employment
    - Description of First Year at UB, 1967/88
    - Birge-Cary Chair
    - Chair - Ziegele
    - Chairs
    - Appointment as Full Librarian
    - Sabbaticals
    - Distinguished Professor Award
    - Interim Appointment, 1968, 1969, 1970
    - Personnel - JBC/Grad School Faculty
    - Recruitment by SUNY/B, 1967
    - Summer Pay, 1969-72
    - Merit Increases
    - Travel Expenses, 1968, 1971 & 1972
    - Workload, 1992
    - Retirement Notice, 22 June 2000
    - UB - Miscellaneous
  - Music Librarianship
    - Compendious Disquistion
    - Music Librarianship Program
    - School of Information and Library Studies (SILS)
    - SILS - Teaching
  - Media Trip '76
  - Instructional Materials
    - LIS 588 Coover Coordinated Collection Development
    - Music 618 - 1st Session
    - Spanish Music - Music Bib. 618 Fall 1968
    - Music 618 - History
- Vassar College, 1953 1967; 1953-1967; VIII (Box 11, Box 12)
  - Vassar College
  - Catalog Research - Grants, Lists, etc.
  - Eileen Thornton, 1956-60
  - Employment, 1953-67
  - Job offers and related, 1951-66
  - List of VC - Duplicates
  - Music Library
  - Music Library Photos, Spring 1967
  - Personnel: Trainee Program
  - President of VC, Publications, Lists, and other material
  - Salmon Fund Grants
  - Stockhousen Analysis
  - Instructional Materials
    - Bibliography Course
    - Medieval Music Instructional Materials
  - Exhibitions
    - 15th Century Music & Music Theory, 1954-10-01 1954-11-30; October-November 1954; 1963-10 1963-10; 1963
    - Baroque Theoretical Treatises, 1959
    - Music in America Mid-19th Century, 1961-02-01 1961-03-31; February-March 1961
    - Notation & the Avant-Garde, 1961-04 1961-05; April-May 1961
    - Government Subsidy, 1962-04 1962-04; April 1962
    - Bach Facsimiles, 1965 1965; Fall 1965
    - Unusual Materials on Beethoven & Mozart, 1966-03 1966-03; March 1966
    - The Stuff of a Music Library, 1966-10 1966-10; October 1966
    - Monteverdi and the Seconda Pratica, 1967-02 1967-02; February 1967
    - Computers & Music, 1967-02 1967-02; February 1967
    - Dictionaries
- Collected publications and research materials, IX (Box 13, Box 14, Box 26)
  - Antiquarian Printed Music: Collecting, Music Printing Methods, Dating Printed Music, by J.J. Lubrano
  - British Public Profiles
  - The Carreno Collection at Vassar College, by Brian Mann
  - Chronicle - MPA Minutes
  - A Curious Collection of Music-Books, Both Vocal and Instrumental
  - Excerpts of Minutes of the Music Publishers' Association (UK) 1881-1908
  - Internet Resources for music/ by Richard Amrhein
  - J. Coover GL4-2968
    Scope and Contents
    Contains photocopies of the original binder, text and notes.
  - Auction and Antiquarian Catalogues (by Dealer)
  - Writings on Music
  - MS Letter from BL
  - Music Sales Catalogues (English)
  - Notes
  - Notes for Music Bibliography Courses - Goldthwaite, Marco, O'Meara, and Coover (for VC)
  - Printing Lecture
  - A Provisional Checklist of Auction Sale Catalogues by the Firm, Leo Liepmannssohn
  - Second List of Writers on Music
  - Sotheby Sales Inventory
  - William Reeves Research Materials
  - Zyklus Lecture Examples
- Publications, 1951 2001; 1951-2001; X (Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22)
  - ACMI - Computing Center
  - ACMI - Correspondence
  - ACMI - Dealer Correspondence
  - ACMI (new) - Notes
  - Antiquarian Catalogs of Interest (unpub.)
  - American Music Librarianship, 1970 1979; 197?
  - Bibliography of Music Bibliographies
  - Book Sept. '01
  - Building an Antiquarian Collection - MLA Meeting (unpub.), 1990
  - Choosing What Not to Preserve
  - Composite Music Manuscripts in Facsimile, 1981
  - Composite Music Manuscripts in Facsimile - Correspondence
  - Computers in Music, 1967
  - Current national Biographies - Krummel Correspondence
  - Current Status of Modern Bibliography - Urbana Panel, 1956
  - Current Status... (in form of Report to ALA), 1956
  - East European Music Periodicals - Cohen
  - East European Music Periodicals - Fedorov
  - Frontschrift
  - Gesamtausgaben
  - Grove's Dictionary
  - Grove's Dictionary of American Music
  - Harvard Symposium, October 1989
  - Jazz - Record Reviewing
  - Kansas Paper - Notes for Revisions
  - Lacunae in Music Dictionaries and Encyclopedias
  - Liep Typescript
  - Maestro's Wastebasket
  - Materials of a Music Library
  - M&R Index - Publication, 1964 ed.
  - Medieval and Renaissance Music on LP - Correspondence with Steven Pallay
  - Medieval and Renaissance Music - 2nd ed., 1962-1971
  - Medieval and Renaissance Music - Provisional Checklist - 1957
  - Music at Auction: Puttick and Simpson (of London), 1794-1971
    - Wessel & Chopin's wks
    - P & S - Misc.
    - Kleinfeldt and Evert tapes - selections
    - Facsimile pages with footnotes
    - Biographical
    - Harvester micro
    - Search for Catalogs
    - Historical
    - Wills
    - Correspondence with British Library, 1979 1984; 1979-1984
    - Correspondence with Knuf
    - Kleinfeldt & Everett
    - Correspondence with Horblit
    - Correspondence with Herrmann
    - Correspondence with McKitterick
    - Plans or arrangement, indexes, etc.
    - Correspondence with Maggs, H. Chifford
    - Chicago university (P&S)
    - Music at Auction Materials (P&S)
    - Leicester Square House - Correspondence - History - Plans
    - Gorzelski correspondence, editing comments, contract
    - Illustrations
    - Permissions - Copies to Elaine, 1987-07-01 1987-07-01; 1987-07-01
    - P&S Questions
    - Locations of Cats.
  - Musical Ephemera - Correspondence
  - Musical Ephemera - Notes
  - Musical Ephemera - Publication
  - Musical Ephemera - Questionnaire
  - Musical instrument collections correspondence
  - Musical instrument collections materials
  - Music Lexicography
  - Music Lexicography, 1987
  - Music Lexicography - U.S. (unpubl)
  - Music Lexicography - U.S. Xeroxes
  - Music Lexicography - 3rd edition, 1971
  - Music Lexicography - Federov
  - Music Lexicography - Hinrichen - Correspondence About
  - Music Librarianship in America
  - Music Publishing, Copyright and Piracy - Drafts, notes, and Correspondence
  - Music Publishing, Copyright & Piracy - Possible Illustrations
  - Music Theory in Translation
  - Music Theory in Translation - Bibliography
  - Music Theory in Translation - Theory Bibliography Supplement
  - New Professor Primer
  - Notes Thing
  - P&S Plate Sales (for Richard Hill book)
  - Photoduplication Services - Report of a Survey, 1951
  - Private Music Instrument Collections: Catalogs and Cognate Literature
    - Excerpt - pages 321-401
    - Correspondence with Grant
    - Outstanding Academic Title Award - correspondence between Gorzelski, Elaine and Rockwood, Irving
    - Notes
    - Correspondence with Ӧsterreichisches Nationalbibliothek & Pinacoteca Nazionale
    - Photo of Brahms from Ӧsterreichisches Nationalbibliothek
    - Fugger Collection
    - Correspondence with Phillips
    - Aylesford - Correspondence with Roberts & Knapp
    - Illustrations
    - Search correspondence
  - PMC/P&S - Materials and Correspondence
  - "Puttick's Auctions" - RMA paper & handout
  - "Puttick's Auctions" (RMA) - Notes & Sources
  - "Puttick's Auctions" (RMA paper) - Corr.
  - Provisional Checklist
  - Publications
  - Published Biographies
  - The "Rainbeau" Catalog: A Facsimile Edition
  - Reference Bibliography in the Music Library (Library Trends) - Correspondence
  - Richard S. Hill: Tributes from Friends
  - Selection Policies for a University Music Library (Acquisitions Article)
  - Smith & Humphries - Supplements
  - Up to the hilt: an index to an unwritten chronicle of the hardcore/ by a person of parts
  - Vassar's Music Library: the First Hundred Years
  - Vassar Paper, October 1991
  - Victorian Periodicals for the Music Trade (Correspondence with Langley, et al)
  - Victorian Periodicals for the Music Trade (Notes)
  - Victorian Periodicals for the Music Trade (Revision for Pub. in Notes)
  - Published Book List
    - Antiquarian Catalogues of Musical Interest
    - A Bibliography of Music Dictionaries
    - Choosing What Not to Preserve
    - East European Music Periodicals
    - Gesamtausgaben
    - Medieval and Renaissance Music on Long-Playing Records, 1964
    - Medieval and Renaissance Music on Long-Playing Records: Supplement, 1962-1971
    - Music at Auction: Puttick and Simpson (of London), 1794-1971
    - Musical Instrument Collections: Catalogues and Cognate Literature
    - Music Lexicography
    - Music Publishing, Copyright and Piracy in Victorian England
    - Photoduplication Services - Report of a Survey, 1951
    - Provisional Checklist of Priced Antiquarians' Catalogues Containing Musical Materials
    - The "Rainbeau" Catalog: A Facsimile Edition
    - Richard S. Hill: Tributes from Friends
- Unpublished materials, 1953 1994; 1953-1994; XI (Box 23, Box 24)
  - Bibliographies
  - Bibliographies of Periodical Publications (1953)
  - Bibliography of Music Bibliography (MS)
  - Guide to Basic Information Sources
  - Guide to Basic Information Sources (1975)
  - Jazz Lectures and Notes (Vassar), circa 1959
  - Published Articles, Essays, Lists, Etc. 1955-1994
  - Published Reviews of Books by J. Coover 1952-1988
  - Record Reviews 1953-1961
  - Reviews of Books on Jazz, 1953-1963
  - Series and Codes for Bibliography of Bibliographies 1953
  - Sources for "Choosing What Not to Preserve" Coover Harvard, 1991
  - Taxonomy of Music Bibliography & Introduction (MSS.)
  - Unpublished Papers, Essays, Lists 1957-1991
  - Up to the Hilt Original 1975
- Manuscripts, XII (Box 25, Box 26)
  - Loose materials
    - Air Mail Special: Benny Goodman, Jimmy Mundy, and Charles, Christian (music)
    - America (My Country, 'Tis of Thee): Original composer unknown, Reverend Samuel Francis Smith (lyrics)
    - Anthropology: Charlie Parker and Dizzy Gillespie (music and lyrics)
    - April in Paris: Vernon Duke (music), Yip Harburg (lyrics)
    - Beautiful Love: Wayne King, Victor Young, and Egbert Van Alstyne (music), Haven Gillespie (lyrics)
    - Button Up Your Overcoat: Ray Henderson (music), B.G. DeSylva and Lew Brown (lyrics)
    - Christmas Song: Mel Tormé and Robert Wells (music and lyrics)
    - Civilization (Bongo, Bongo, Bongo): Bob Hilliard and Carl Sigman (words and music)
    - Did I Remember: Walter Donaldson (music), Harold Adamson (lyrics)
    - Encore, Cherie: Tex Beneke (music and lyrics)
    - Flamingo: Ted Grouya (music), Edmund Anderson (lyrics)
    - Ghost of a Chance: Victor Young (music), Ned Washington and Bing Crosby (lyrics)
    - Good Bait: Tad Dameron (music)
    - I May Be Wrong, But I Think You're Wonderful (Arr. by Red Evans): Henry Sullivan (music), Harry Ruskin (lyrics)
    - I Told Ya' I Love Ya, Now Get Out: Herb Ellis, Johnny Frigo and Lou Carter (music and lyrics)
    - I'll Remember April: Gene de Paul (music), Patricia Johnston and Don Raye (lyrics)
    - If I Had You: James Campbell, Reginald Connelly, and Ted Shapiro (music and lyrics)
    - Love and the Weather: Irving Berlin (music and lyrics)
    - My Little Boy: Nellie Lutcher (music and lyrics)
    - Ol' Man Rebop: Floyd Wilson (music)
    - On a Slow Boat to China: Frank Loesser (music and lyrics)